First of all, the first new feature is the update of our UI interface.
In the new version of Marvelous Designer, our UV editor has been regarded as a main window.
So you can directly switch the UV editor and our 2D version window here.
Or we can put the UV editor and other window brands together as the main window for inspection.
I use one display here, and if you have multiple displays, you can put it on the secondary screen.
Our new version of the UV window has also updated some content.
For example, when we select an object material, we can directly switch to its attribute editor.
Or if we choose a tool, for example, a button tool, the object window will also automatically locate the physical attribute of the button.
We can make some adjustment to the attribute of the button.
That includes some other things like buttons, buttons, eyes, lines, etc.
Then as a secondary window, our history record or the new module library can be placed on both sides of our screen as a secondary screen.
These windows can also be independently created or combined.
Just like the UI layout changes in our previous version.
These layout changes can be done by everyone.
For example, we can change the layout to a layout setting and then call it.
In the new version, we have also updated the asset library.
In addition to the new asset files, we have also added some new tree types.
For example, now there are updates to virtual models or some scenes.
And now the selection is also more intuitive than the previous selection.
As for the default files,
we can find them in the old version of the window.
I will introduce them to you later.
And then we have added a lot of fabric files.
These are the fabric files in the second version.
For example,
For the previous version of the fabric files,
we can find them in the Legacy folder in the Fabric folder.
Select Legacy on the left side.
I'm sorry, everyone.
I have a cold recently.
So you may hear me coughing all the time.
In the new version,
we have updated some water-washing text.
These can also be used directly.
And then we have added some new butterfly file previews.
And in our scene,
we have also added some scene files that you can use to make some effects.
And then the default files that came out before.
You can go back to the asset library.
Click the bottom left corner of this.
Go back to the old picture window.
Find the old files.
So don't worry about the old files.
We still have them.
Including the HANA that you often use.
It is also placed in our previous picture window.
Then we have the array list here.
You can classify it by type,
or by row,
or by row or by row.
Or you can switch to display its details.
For example,
such as the name or date.
Then click the preview in the right side.
You can see the three-dimensional picture of each file,
If there is a file that does not have a three-dimensional picture, it means that we may not have downloaded this file, so we have to click download to download it.
Because our library window has some new updated content, you may need to download it from outside.
After downloading, we can see its three-dimensional picture in the preview window on the right.
Then on the right side of our library window, there is our Connect business city.
Here we can directly call the files in our business city in Marvelous Designer.
In the default situation, it only shows the free file.
Then you can directly call these materials according to your needs.
We don't need to go to Connect business city to download again.
Cough
Here, for example, we have an online file.
If we want to call this file, we can directly double-click it and download it from the background and load these clothing files or other material files in the current project file.
In addition, when we select an object material, there will be a corresponding Connect business city page in the upper left corner.
We can also quickly go to this page.
Then we can call some digital assets in Connect business city.
Also, including our name line, we can directly call it.
So now we are in the new version of the asset library.
These free assets, compared to before, we can import these files faster and use them.
In addition,
If we have already downloaded a file, we can copy its path and then create a new library window by adding and creating a new library window.
To integrate these materials into your library.
For example, I am here to directly call the file folder downloaded by Connect for the new library window.
So we can directly find these files that I have downloaded and then manage them uniformly.
The next new feature is our module library.
In addition to some new module types, our module library has also undergone a major change.
For example, when I select a module library, I can find the clothing type I need.
Then after selecting the clothing type, we can call these component modules at the bottom.
Like these component modules.
After we match them together, we can start the simulation.
Then we can automatically wear it on our virtual model.
Of course, your posture should match our module as much as possible.
If we want to change the module, we can directly double click to change the different modules.
For example, like our collar.
Then if I make adjustments to one of the modules and I want to register it as a module that can be changed later.
We just need to click on the plus sign to select it.
After selecting these modules, for example, I have selected these sleeve modules now.
Then click on the enter button to register it.
When registering, you can change its name or its shrink chart.
All these defaults are already set.
Just click on OK.
Here we can check the sewing.
Then include the name of this sleeve.
Because the sleeve is a sleeve.
Let's look at the green part now.
After we confirm it, just click on OK.
Then you can easily switch these components that have been registered as module components.
For example, now I want to replace the sleeves.
Then I can directly double-click on other sleeve styles to replace them.
Then this module that has been registered as a component.
In the new version, we can achieve the configuration of different styles.
For example, I now change a shoulder sleeve.
Or some other.
For example, like a short sleeve.
This is the material that has been registered.
Then I go to change its front or back.
You can see that there is still a sewing line between the sleeves and the waistband.
So in the new version of the module library, we also do not have the previous module frame.
Because now it is through the components to identify it.
Automatically create these sewing lines between the components and the components.
It will not be like before.
It is a binding through the components and module frames.
So when we switch to different clothing types.
We can quickly call the previously created clothing files.
Then if we want to quickly select this one from other component windows.
We can just share this component to other clothing types.
This is not only suitable for models of Marvelous Designers.
Just because of our component.
I use this model to record the video.
If you are a model created by yourself.
You can also customize your clothing.
Later you will see how I use this function to create our Hanfu.
Now, for example, I change a clothing type.
Like polo shirt.
When I call the front and collar of the polo shirt.
It can also keep the previous lantern sleeve.
Then the next is a set of Hanfu.
In fact, Hanfu.
Here it is as a new category.
We will add it in.
Hanfu is actually a lot of times.
Do you think the Hanfu version is very difficult?
In fact, the Hanfu version.
You can imagine it in ancient times.
It is relatively horizontal and vertical.
Not that there are many points of curve.
That's a lot of times.
It may be a change of some sleeves.
Or the transformation of the collar.
Through our new clothing module.
The function of the clothing module and the parts.
We can go to the Hanfu.
For example, the front and back.
And the collar and the sleeves are separated.
So that we can achieve it.
Through the combination of many parts.
To complete the creation of different Hanfu.
The length of the sleeves and the clothes.
Do not match.
You can change it.
That is, you can quickly call.
This plate.
When its length is not right.
Because the sewing line is already matched.
So you just change the length.
Change the plate shape.
Okay.
In this case.
We will use the module generation mechanism.
Quick.
It's like a quick selection.
Define different parts.
Because now we have a Hanfu.
We have to redefine the parts of each part.
Like the front is two red parts.
Then we also define it for the back.
The collar is all white plates.
Here we choose all the collar plates.
Then press enter to confirm.
Define the clothing.
Which plates are the same?
Which plates are the same in the front?
The back, the collar and the sleeves.
After we registered.
On the left side.
You will see different module matching.
Okay.
After that.
For example.
You can change the sleeves.
And then the added.
This sleeve file.
To be added as a module component.
And then.
You can save the module configuration.
The module configuration.
In fact, it means.
You change the clothes.
Because some clothes.
The style.
It may be all styles.
No collar.
Then we will.
Define a new style type.
And then.
Just use the existing.
Module configuration.
Sorry.
Okay.
After that.
You can continue to make other adjustments.
For example.
The hanfu.
We sometimes.
It may be a small sleeve.
With a.
Um.
Divide.
Divide the collar.
Like this.
Or even if we.
Adjust the size of other parts.
Then we can still keep.
The sleeve part.
That is.
As long as it is.
The length of the sleeve.
Is almost the same.
You can go directly.
Use.
Of course.
The length of your sleeve.
Even if it doesn't match.
You can also quickly.
To modify it.
To modify the sleeve.
Do it.
Look.
We can.
Try to.
To.
To make it.
Not too long.
Okay.
I will.
You can.
Use.
The.
Dive.
FBX.
If it doesn't have a name.
Well.
Wait a minute.
I'm going to stop.
Dive.
FBX.
If it doesn't have a name.
Then you can.
There are.
Hook choices.
Good.
And then.
What about.
It doesn't have an IK joint, so you can set the IK joint manually in Marvelous Designer.
For example, we can define the head and waist, or you can choose to automatically print it with one click.
It will print the IK joint of Marvelous Designer.
Yes, you can make your own IK joint.
After you create the IK joint, if you want to use it on a computer, you just need to pack all the files in the IK joint and take them away.
Here, after we have automatically printed it, you can choose to set the T-shape position.
The T-shape position means that your model is embedded in the T-shape position.
Then you can set the current T-shape position and register it as a T-shape position.
Instead of using this function to break your model into a T-shape,
when you import it, you have to first change the model to a T-shape and then register the T-shape position.
I will show you the wrong case later.
After setting the T-shape position, the reset button next to it will light up.
After the T-shape is lit up, it means that you are now bound.
After binding, you can directly call Marvelous Designer.
These actions in our asset library.
Because now we are joint printing.
The print is Marvelous Designer's own IK joint.
So no matter what your model is, how is its bone structure?
After we finish the IK print, we can call Marvelous Designer's posture.
Then, for example, now.
I use an A-pose posture.
But I choose to set the T-shape position.
Then we can take a look at the reset position.
It will reset to A-pose.
But at this time, because we registered it as a T-pose.
So it may have.
When we import a file with an A-shape position,
its posture will have some problems.
This is because we just registered an A-pose model as a T-pose.
So everyone must pay attention to your model.
When you import it, it is a T-shape.
After that, because our asset library has already supported the IK joint point.
So everyone can adjust the virtual model's posture more freely.
Then when you change the virtual model's posture.
You can put some positions where you don't want it to rotate.
To lock the rotation or movement of the joint.
These.
Save it as your own pose.
First, your model is transferred to Marvelous Designer.
After that.
If you want to use the IK joint to print.
The virtual model is already.
Is to print the position in Marvelous Designer.
To print the IK joint point.
Then after printing.
The file in the upper left corner is saved as a virtual model.
After that, it is AVT.
It is the AVT format of Marvelous Designer.
Then you can go.
To the other positions.
Then if you want to go to other 3D software.
To use this pose.
Then.
Then you can't use AVT.
Because it is a special virtual model of Marvelous Designer.
But you can.
Show that OBJ model or FBX model.
Then.
For example.
We are now.
If you lock the joint point.
Then IK everyone knows.
After you lock it.
It can't move.
You can unlock it.
Then you can move again.
Then because we have already printed the IK joint point.
So.
The model on this maximum.
It can also be directly transferred to Marvelous Designer.
The action file inside.
That is, we pre-set some action files.
You can also directly transfer it to this virtual model.
So no matter which three-way platform you are from.
It just.
As long as it has Google information.
We can give it to him.
Marvelous Designer.
The IK joint sound.
Then.
After this animation.
You can use the animation of the joint point.
It doesn't matter.
That's like me.
For example.
Now I have one.
The virtual model with action downloaded from Maxamo.
I can also put it.
Now the action.
Registered as.
With Marvelous Designer.
Virtual model.
Or Marvelous Designer.
IK joint point matching.
An action file.
Then here.
You can choose the virtual model first.
The gender.
But it doesn't matter.
Whether it's a man or a woman.
The information between them.
IK.
Is shared.
So you.
Even if this model itself.
It has no gender.
You can also give it to him first.
Define.
Select a virtual model.
Gender.
Then select.
Transfer.
Automatic transfer.
Virtual model.
Gender.
And then.
You can also.
Use the action of the virtual model.
Okay.
After the registration.
You can save it.
The action we just transferred.
For example.
I used one before.
A stranger.
Then I gave him.
I just chose a gender.
I chose a male.
Then.
Like this action.
Because it is to identify.
IK joint point.
So even if we change one now.
As long as the joint is printed.
The model.
He can.
Go directly.
Use this action file.
Okay.
What's next.
The key point animation.
In the new version.
Of Marvelous Designer.
We support.
For many attributes.
You can.
K.
The first one.
Is the virtual model.
Position.
Okay.
For example.
At the beginning.
When we.
T-pose.
Give him.
Insert a key point.
After that.
We're going to call.
A.
Position.
Okay.
After adjustment.
We'll give him.
Insert another key point.
That.
Like us.
The animation between the two key points.
It is.
So.
Through.
Different.
Key.
Point.
Animation.
We can.
Realize.
Virtual model.
Action.
And some.
Animation.
Recording.
That.
Like me.
Is.
In.
Three.
Position.
At the beginning.
Added a key point.
And then.
In the middle.
When.
Changing.
Position.
Added a key point.
That.
Position.
Then.
We can.
Adjust.
You.
Hope.
At.
The.
Point.
His.
Action.
Is.
The.
Position.
You.
Set.
The.
Action.
Appearance.
Position.
Here.
We.
In.
The.
Bone.
Client.
Point.
His.
Key.
Position.
At.
The.
Hammer.
This.
And.
The.
You.
Can.
To.
Out.
You.
Stand.
On.
The.
Hole.
Here.
Is.
That.
Position.
Is.
In.
The.
Box.
Or.
The.
Client.
Then you can also set the state of the fixed needle.
In fact, we have the old version of the fixed needle K needle.
It's just that in the new version,
we add some of the new animation of our key needle,
such as adjusting the position of the key needle,
and some of these attribute adjustments.
So this is to show you how I deal with this situation.
I may choose to activate the key needle in reverse at the beginning,
and then record the needle in reverse.
And then in the middle, I want to activate it,
and then give it a K needle.
Through the key needle animation of the fixed needle,
I can realize that in a certain period of time,
I want to fix a certain part.
And then here is a mistake demonstration.
That is, because I am in the middle of this needle,
I hit the key needle with the fixed needle.
Then in the middle,
in this case,
because I chose to fix the fixed needle to the virtual model,
it will match the joint point to the virtual model body.
In this case,
you need to know that it is now matched.
For example, the point it is now facing is the point of your finger.
If you choose to record in other places,
there may be some problems.
That is, you add the fixed needle under this needle,
and then use the fixed needle to the virtual model body.
You'd better hit the key needle under this needle.
For example,
I'm not going to record the key needle under this needle now,
but choose to add a key needle to it in the front.
In fact, the point we just placed,
it will be near the mouth position.
Now, if I give it a record at the beginning,
if the fixed needle is already activated,
its position will be moved directly to the mouth position.
This is a mistake demonstration.
You may have to pay attention when you do it in the future.
If you do this,
it may go to the mouth position at once,
from the beginning to the mouth position.
So you have to be sure
when you want to attach the fixed needle.
If you want to do it from the beginning,
this fixed needle is...
How to say?
Because the fixed needle,
when you attach the fixed needle to the virtual model,
it automatically detects the virtual model grid closest to the fixed needle.
So if you want to attach it to the hand position,
you have to move this fixed needle first,
move it from the virtual model body,
and then attach it back.
So I just want to remind you.
You may have to pay a little attention when you are operating.
Of course, if you encounter any problems,
you can leave a comment in the comment area,
or you can ask me in the QQ group.
Then, in the previous version,
the wind control machine can be K-injected.
In the new version,
the wind control machine can also be K-injected.
These properties can be K-injected separately.
For example, like the activation of these properties.
If you don't K-inject it separately,
but directly choose to K-inject it in the wind control machine,
it will record all the K-injections at once.
So in most cases,
you don't even have to click on the purple bar,
just directly choose to K-inject it in the wind control machine.
If you want to slightly adjust some K-injections for it,
you can open the purple bar.
Then, including the rotation of the wind control machine,
and the position of the wind control machine,
you can use the K-injection to make it change the line.
Then, in the wind control machine,
Then, including the intensity of the wind,
in the case of a default,
the key pins we open are all linear.
So in the middle,
you will find that its intensity is gradually from 100 to 200.
I'm sorry.
For the intensity here,
if you want it to change suddenly when it reaches the key pin position,
you need to set the previous key pin as continuous.
In this way, it will continue this value until the next key pin appears.
So you will see that the intensity here
is directly from 100 to 200 instantly.
It doesn't jump over gradually.
If you choose three times,
its algorithm is three times.
The algorithm of the three-time equation
is not a linear transformation.
So if you choose three times,
you will find that the further it goes,
the stronger the change.
Then the first half of the change may be more flat.
You should understand this, right?
Three-time equation.
Then there is another one.
Our plant can also be changed.
Plants have two animation bars.
One is the change of material.
The change of material,
because in Marvelous Descendants,
finally, if you are involved in the exit,
for example,
material change,
you can do the gradient color.
For example,
from pink gradient to red,
but because you finally exit,
its material is only one.
The needle you exit,
which material is used,
it is which one.
So if you exit at the end,
this effect is also impossible to exit.
It can only be seen in Marvelous Descendants.
So under normal circumstances,
like the change of material,
we recommend that you
may do a preview.
This function is mainly used
in physical properties.
For physical properties,
like here,
when I insert a key needle,
I can choose to put this
material property,
because this is a material key needle,
I can reduce its
strength at the end.
For example,
here,
I have reduced its strength at the end
to a very low level,
because my
square material material
is completed by pressure.
Then everyone should know that
like this pressure property,
your fabric stretching strength,
that is, the stretching performance,
for example,
like the strength,
the resistance,
the tension,
these,
it will,
under the same strength,
the better your stretching performance,
it will definitely expand more and more.
So we are in the
case of the same strength,
the better the stretching performance,
the stronger it will be.
So we are here,
its physical properties,
such as the strength at the end,
the tension at the end,
when it is reduced,
its stretching performance
will be better.
So under the same
energy pressure,
it will expand more and more.
We can take a look at
the actual effect later.
Then about the
physical properties,
I have talked about it
in the previous live broadcast.
You can go back and
take a look at
the previous live broadcast.
Well,
like this,
our
strength at the end
is gradually reduced.
So you will see
this ball,
it will have one
from
a more
regular
square body,
square body
into an
expanding ball.
This is because
our pressure
is the same.
In the same situation,
you go to its
strength at the end,
open a needle,
it will gradually
become easier to stretch.
It will have
the effect of expanding
like this.
Then you can go back and
take a look at
the actual effect.
And,
you can also
K-striking the plate.
If you do K-striking the plate,
other than the plate
mentioned in
the previous version,
the plate
where it is,
you can go to K-striking it.
You can also
make it a
physical property
and call it
K-striking.
For example,
we have two pieces of fabric now.
We have to give this leaf
to let it call
the physical property
of the A-flat
first,
and then call
the physical property
of the B-flat.
You can use
the physical property
of the B-flat
to complete
the K-striking
of the fabric
for this plate
K-striking.
For example,
at the beginning,
I used
the A-flat
for it.
Then,
in the middle
half,
I used
the second
piece of red
fabric for it.
The K-striking
in the middle,
let me mention
again,
this keystriking
is linear
transformation
when it is defaulted.
Don't forget
to
remember
that
the linear
transformation
and the continuous
are different.
If you want
it to change
instantly,
that is,
instantly
from pink
to red,
or its physical property
is instantly
from one number
to another number,
you may have to
set the previous
keystriking
as continuous.
Then,
here,
for its weight,
I am
increasing
the weight
of the red
fabric
to the highest.
In the same
wind resistance
or weight
situation,
when its weight
is particularly high,
it will fall
faster than the
side fabric.
So,
you will see
that the two
completely
identical
petals
and the red
one
will fall
faster.
Because
the middle
is linear
transformation,
if I pull
the keystriking
back a little,
the time it
drifts
will be
slower
for it
to change
and change
the effect
.
And
just to
mention
it again,
if you want
it to
continue
to be
pink
in the first half,
the middle
suddenly
becomes
red,
set the previous
keystriking
as continuous.
Then
there is
the simulation property.
You must remember that
in the simulation property,
you must
set the preset
option to
self-definition.
If
you use
some of
our default
settings,
such as
normal speed
or animation,
there will be a warning
here,
reminding you
not to record,
just not
to this
animation property
plus
K.
It's not that you can't
record animation,
it's just that you can't
K.
Then you change to user
self-definition,
and now
you only have
these two K.
One is
air resistance,
and the other is
gravity.
For example,
here,
I set the gravity
to zero at the beginning,
I can insert a keystriking
first and
then change the gravity
to
negative 9800
at the end.
This
gives the
3D environment
a gravity
effect.
At the beginning,
it doesn't have
gravity.
We
also
change it
So at the beginning, the petal won't move because there is no gravity in the entire 3D environment.
Then, because we hit the negative 9800, the negative 9800 gravity needle will automatically fall off afterwards.
This is recording! I didn't, the upper left corner has a pause.
I recorded it during the whole operation, but my explanation is a live explanation.
Okay, the next new feature is, this should be the front, the UV that supports the side and back now.
Okay, in the new version, first of all, everyone must remember that if you want to adjust the side and back UV,
you must,
you must remember to open the thick texture surface.
The thick texture surface, when you open it, there will be the back and side UV in the UV editor.
The side UV follows the front, the back is a little bit independent.
I didn't, I didn't actually speed up, I just recorded the video.
Okay.
Then, including our side UV, it is like this, because it follows the front, it is directly generated along the side of the front to be completed.
Then, if we adjust the thickness of the texture surface, you will see that the side UV will become thicker and wider.
Then, including our thickness of the texture surface, it will also affect the side surface of the plate.
Okay.
This plate is actually the thickness of the side.
So if you change the thickness of the fabric, you will see the side UV in the UV editor, it will become thicker and wider.
Then, if you switch back to the texture surface, you will see that the UV on the back is gone.
So everyone must remember to remind everyone again, if you want to use the side and back UV, remember to change the display type in the 3D window to the dense texture surface.
Then, the next new feature is the hair filter.
In the new version, we support some hair effects in the 3D window in Marvelous Designer.
Whether you turn on the high-quality model or not, you can see the hair in the 3D window.
Because in fact, it still takes up some computing power to predict hair.
So we can use it again.
So we can set a hair type in the user-designed window to display it.
Here in the 3D window, you can choose to display the shape of the hair filter.
For example, the original column, the flat surface, or the line.
The original column is the one with the largest resolution of the side thickness, width, and the maximum resolution of the stand.
Because it is three-dimensional.
The flat surface is that your hair has a width and a length.
Okay.
It also has a length.
But it doesn't have the thickness of the side.
The line is the one with the hair in the 3D window.
Oh, it's okay.
The hair can be pulled out.
But the hair only supports the projection of the USB file format.
And then you can use some preset according to the type of hair.
Yeah.
This Hanf button is also completed in Marvelous Designer.
I made this button with the template.
And then I put it in as a component.
Oh, it seems to be put in as a button.
And then you can also modify the color of the hair.
And you can also put some basic texture pictures of the hair to control its color.
And below is the hair color.
If the hair color is black, it is related to the hair.
In real life, the color of your hair is actually influenced by black and white.
It's black and black.
Black and black.
Red and black.
And then in Marvelous Designer, the degree of blackness controls your hair.
It's a gradient.
It's white.
It's the original color.
It's a gradient.
If you turn the color green to a brown tone, then the brown will turn black at a certain degree.
So if the degree of blackness of your hair is zero, it's the original color.
For example, blue.
And then one is blue plus black, and it turns black.
In the middle, it will be a brown.
For example, 0.5 is the effect of blue plus brown.
And then the red degree of control is actually the degree of blackness of hair.
That is, it's already a brown part.
the degree of black and white is 0, no matter how you change the degree of red, it will not affect it,
and then the brightness is the overall hair. The higher the brightness, the stronger its brightness is,
and then the lower the brightness, the overall brightness of its reflection will not be very strong,
and then the degree of light is affected by the part that is already smooth, which is the brightness. It is
an additional effect, that is, the higher the value, the overall hair will look smoother,
it will be a relatively obvious concentration of a contrast effect, that is, the higher the degree of light,
the darker it will be, and then the bright place will be more concentrated. The next is the hair color change,
which is actually the setting of the hair root, which is the color of the middle and top,
so you can see the hair will be adjusted and the color will be set,
and then in addition to setting this color,
you can also go to set our hair's hair conditioning color.
Its accenting position is
good
when the color was adjusted here,
there is a difference between the bottom if you open it it will be a shifting,
There is no cross-section in the middle.
Next is the hair shape.
The hair shape is actually easier to understand.
The basics are the length and thickness of the hair.
These are all easier to understand.
The bend is the hair.
Is it easy to bend?
The higher the value, the closer it is to 1, the easier it is to bend.
The more it sticks to the added plane.
The lower the value, the closer it is to 0.
It will resist the bending effect.
The width is the difference between the width between the root and the top of the plate.
The width is getting narrower and narrower.
The density is the density of the hair.
In fact, it is easier to understand about the basic form.
The number of sections is the number of sections of the hair.
If your hair is curly,
that is,
if there are more hair curls behind the bend,
or if the bend is higher,
you have to adjust the number of sections
to make it softer.
There will be a basic sticker below.
The basic sticker has the effect of hair loss.
Hair loss is directly passed
through the length chart in our generator
to control the length of each section of the hair.
Because the black area of ​​the length chart
will make this part of its hair short,
so it will form the effect of one section at a time.
The higher the reduction effect,
you will see that the black part is more.
The entire hair is straightened,
and then one section at a time will be more concentrated.
Then if you reduce the intensity,
its reduction effect will be higher.
In other words,
its reduction effect,
that is,
the effect of shortening the hair,
will be a little weaker.
Then what about this randomness?
In fact,
you can see that it is the contrast of this length chart sticker.
If you pull it to the highest,
its contrast is the strongest,
that is,
the effect of each section will be more obvious.
In fact,
these properties are all used to control this length chart.
The length chart will finally be added to our hair.
Then there will be a cutting chart here.
I have added a black part of the cutting chart to everyone.
Then the cutting chart has two modes.
In fact,
it is a chart added to the length chart above.
You can go to the setting of this added chart.
Its participation,
for example,
it is thicker.
If it is thicker,
you can see this chart.
Its black part is more.
The black part from top to bottom.
Then the hair on it will be shorter.
The hair below will maintain the previous length.
This low area,
the height of this low area,
in fact,
is the setting of its darker color,
that is,
the part of the hair that is more powerful,
or the part of the hair that maintains more length.
The proportion of these.
Then there is also a curved direction chart.
It looks like a hair line sticker.
In fact,
it is used to control these hair strands.
They are facing each other.
Because hair hair vinegar,
sometimes it is facing the same direction.
But sometimes it will be messy hair.
One hair strand at a time,
it will not be the same direction.
So we can use this curved direction chart.
To control how messy this hair is.
Then you can see that.
In the modification,
for example,
when the direction is random,
we may give this hair line sticker.
Applying different.
The effect of this hair line.
It also includes intensity random.
You will see that.
Some parts of its hair line effect.
It is not so strong.
Then there are some parts.
It will have a large section.
A large section of hair line effect.
In fact,
they all affect your hair.
Its curved direction.
It is the direction of hair vinegar.
You can use this picture.
To see its final effect.
Preview the effect in the 3D window.
Then you can apply it.
The detail of hair vinegar.
It controls.
This hair strand by strand.
It is independent.
This is the effect of hair vinegar.
For example,
I put hair vinegar here.
When the detail intensity is very high.
You can see that.
The direction chart.
It is very strong.
All the hair is blown away.
So you can.
Through this hair vinegar generator.
To achieve different.
The effect of hair vinegar.
Below.
There is a gravity.
The gravity.
In fact,
it also affects your hair.
The effect of a curved.
For example.
This pull value.
In fact,
it is the value of gravity.
The higher this value.
Its.
It will stick more.
Your.
The surface of the costume.
Then this value is relatively low.
Because the weight of hair.
The effect of gravity.
It is relatively weak.
Then it can.
Cool down.
The following three directions.
It is.
Look at this plane.
Its X-axis.
It is the direction of the horizontal direction.
Or the Y-axis.
It is.
The vertical direction.
The Z-axis.
Then the vertical direction.
The first.
The vertical direction.
Yes.
Can control the orientation.
Its.
This force.
The direction of the hair.
Not.
3D window.
And.
We change the color.
After that.
It is.
It can control its.
Curving rate.
Curve rate.
Like this.
The radius.
Is.
The hair.
Circulated.
This is a small roll.
Or big roll.
Then the quantity.
The degree of curl.
If you have more hair in the radius, it must be more powerful.
The direction of the hair line is controlled by the direction of the hair loss effect that you have generated.
It regulates the direction of the hair loss by the direction of the hair line.
Where does it bend?
Where does it fall?
Can you understand?
Because the hair line is controlled by one direction.
Next is the irregularity.
For example, if you set the irregularity of the length, it will be long and short.
If the irregularity is 0, it will use the same value.
Next are some small functions.
The first is the improvement of the automatic four-sided measurement.
In the new version, we have made a change to the automatic four-sided measurement.
In the previous version, if we use the four-sided measurement to optimize this function,
you will see that there are still some five-sided measurements.
And its grid arrangement
may not be so reasonable.
So in the new version, we also optimized the automatic four-sided measurement function.
In the automatic four-sided measurement function,
first of all, our calculation speed has changed.
Another one is the four-sided measurement of the current arrangement.
It reduces the occurrence of five-sided.
The four-sided measurement arrangement will be more reasonable.
After that, we will continue to optimize the four-sided measurement.
Then in the new version,
our display frame is separated from other clothing rendering types.
So we can stack different clothing rendering types and display frames.
Unlike before, there are only two options.
One is the white line frame,
and the other is the texture surface line frame.
We will explore other ones later.
Then for the display frame rendering,
like in the new version,
the display frame rendering is a type of 3D render
that allows you to render a 3D graphic
of the current clothing effect.
It is a 2D rendering type.
And then we can also use the quick photo function to drag it out.
Then I saw the chat, the guy just asked, isn't this hair line just a hairline that can control the image?
It controls your hair.
That is to say, because the hair line has a curve effect, it is from your hair, for example, your hair line is in this position.
It's like this.
It's blue and purple here.
This is light blue.
It's the hair that falls over like this.
Then the style picture rendering function.
With this function, we can
show the line frame separately.
Then you just use the black and white background,
you use the black and white surface,
and then stack them to show the line frame.
For style picture rendering,
you can see it in our 3D window.
For example, we can set the outline line,
the thickness of the opening line,
and then the bright line.
We can increase the proportion of the bright line.
After increasing the proportion,
the effect of the bright line will be more obvious.
In fact, it is used to
quickly check your style effect.
For example,
we use the style picture rendering function,
and then use the quick photo
to extract these pictures.
After that,
we can use it as a preview.
For example,
if you want to put the file
in the Connect mall,
you can use this to make a cover picture.
It's more intuitive.
Then you can also set
the color of the line,
or the texture of the clothing.
For the texture of the clothing,
if you choose the texture,
you can change the texture
according to the style of the clothing.
Then if you choose the color,
it will show the surface of the clothing
with one color.
Then we can go to the quick photo page.
For the quick photo page,
you can select
the 3D window of the single page
and try to select the color
of the 3D window.
For example,
you can select the picture
under this lens,
or select the picture
under multiple images.
You can see that
it is based on the clothing
in your current 3D window.
So you can switch
the clothing rendering type
to another rendering type.
Then you refresh it,
and you can extract the effect
in the current 3D window.
You may be wondering
what this function is for.
You can also set the 3D background
to green
and turn it into a green wood.
This way,
after you extract the video,
you can turn it into
a 3D effect.
Because there is a video extract function.
Next,
this small new function
is for automatic rendering.
First, you need to
put these images
on the layout of the virtual model.
After that,
we can use the
automatic rendering function
in the 3D window.
Here, you need to select the clothing type,
such as pants or skirt.
If it is a pants,
you click pants,
and then confirm.
After that,
you can see that
there is a skirt
and some belts.
Then,
because of this pants,
for example,
if your pants
does not have a belt,
it does not matter.
As long as you make sure
that these pants
have been placed on the layout,
even if there is a rendering line
between them,
it will identify the location of your layout.
So, you must make sure
that the location of your layout is reasonable.
The next is to
mix the texture of the stickers.
In the previous version,
the stickers
will be added to the
top of the clothing
to cover the original texture.
This makes
some of the areas
where the stickers are used,
such as the hair line,
are brought by the stickers themselves.
In the new version,
our stickers
are also made into 3D materials.
So, when you edit
a sticker type,
there will be a window
where you can find
the corresponding sticker type.
Then, you can adjust
the entire sticker.
For example,
your sticker is on the clothing.
For example, your home has a small badge.
This badge has this small badge in many places.
Then, it will be changed once.
Then, in our
digital printer,
there will be a sticker
with the same texture as the fabric.
Here, you can see that
I added a modified picture.
It has no texture at all.
So, after you add it,
it doesn't have the effect of the hair line sticker.
But the texture of the clothing at the bottom
itself has the effect of the hair line sticker.
So, here I directly
choose a sticker with the same texture as the fabric.
It will use the same hair line sticker
with the texture of the fabric.
Then, when we use the
homebay software,
this part has the texture of the
texture of the texture of the texture.
The next is the setting of the
body pressure chart.
In the new version,
there are three types of body pressure chart.
One is the hard pressure chart,
the other is the hard change chart,
and the other is the body pressure chart.
The hard pressure chart
is a fabric itself.
After it is transformed
into the body pressure chart,
it receives the value of the external force.
The hard pressure chart is the
value of the transformation of this area
after it receives the external force.
It is a proportion of its transformation.
The body pressure chart
requires you to open the simulation.
After opening the simulation,
you will see
which positions it is
receiving some force
after the clothing is simulated on the human body.
For example,
we can set your clothing here.
After it receives the force,
if the transformation is more powerful
or when it receives more force,
it shows the color.
How many colors can you set?
For example,
choose four or eight colors.
Then,
like the hard pressure chart
or the hard change chart,
there will be a pattern type below.
You can choose to follow the area
or to change it.
If it is a division,
in the middle,
it is not affected by the external force.
There are some changes.
For example,
it is not so close to the body.
It may not have color.
But if you choose to change,
there will be some changes in the middle.
Then,
you can choose the pattern type.
You can also choose the grid point
or the face of the whole.
There will be some changes
on one side.
The face will be more obvious.
Next,
it is the display.
This point is important to mention.
There are three directions of display.
The tail sand,
the gold sand,
and the angle line.
This is the fabric.
The tail sand is the gold sand.
Usually,
the vertical direction
is the gold sand
and the horizontal direction is the tail sand.
If you turn on these displays,
you will see
which part of the tail sand
is affected
and which part is removed.
So,
you can use the switch
to find out
whether the horizontal direction
is too tight
or the vertical direction
is too tight.
For example,
this dress
is very red.
I don't know
if the vertical direction
is too tight
or the horizontal direction
or the angle line.
I will turn on and off
the angle line
here.
Actually,
you can see
that the gold sand
on the sleeves
or the chest
is very small.
That means
this dress
is too tight
in terms of width.
So,
you can use
the tail sand
and the angle line
to find out
whether this dress
is too tight
in terms of
the shoulder
or the chest.
For example,
this dress
is too tight
in terms of the shoulder
or the chest.
So,
you can use
the angle line
to find out
whether this dress
is too tight
or the angle line
in terms of the shoulder
in terms of the chest.
For the other dress,
I will use
the angle line
to find out
whether it is too tight
in terms of the shoulder
or the angle line.
If the angle line
is too tight
in terms of the shoulder
or the angle line,
you can turn
the angle line
In the past, I don't know if you guys have seen it, but when you export an Alembic file, you will find that the Alembic file will be very large.
Obviously, the number of your actions is very small, but the whole file is still very large.
Sometimes it may be because you have added a private line.
So in the new version, we can optimize its network number by optimizing the multilinear grid of the private line.
Of course, you don't have to press the network number very low at once.
You can lower it a little bit, for example, down to 30.
So that it can maintain the network grid to a certain extent, and it can still have the effect of the private line.
Of course, if you do animation, because the private line network grid will record the movement of the top of the network grid.
So that's what makes your file very large.
If you want to completely optimize the size of the entire file, then you should still use the 2D private line.
Don't use the 3D one.
Then there is a change in our 2D private line.
For example, now you use a physical private line.
Of course, I use a special one.
I just use this one block at a time.
In this case, you can use the edit private line function to select an independent private line.
You have to pay attention to this.
You don't choose the private line type.
In Marvelous Designer, when you choose a type, that is, when you choose a material type in the physical window, you are going to modify some specific specifications of the entire material type.
For example, the length of the private line, the thickness of the private line.
But this kind of corner position, is it smooth?
Or is it a distance away from the Z-axis?
You may have the same size private line in a different position.
It's different.
I'll give you an example.
For example, you're in some chest, under the night, it's easy to stretch and deform.
Or the neck, this kind of, just all kinds of positions.
His private line may stretch and deform.
You may have to pay more attention to some of his settings.
Then if you're in the pocket, or some of his length is not very good.
Uh, those positions with obvious deformities.
Maybe you can just use the default, that is, the unified specifications.
So I'm just reminding you.
This open smooth function is set after you select a private line.
After opening the smooth, if you turn off the smooth here, you will see.
If you don't open the smooth, it's because there's a gap in the middle of this picture.
It's a rectangular, rectangular, independent one.
It's not a fan or a chase.
To put the gap in the middle.
Just let it fit together.
It's an independent, independent picture.
So if you open the smooth, it's going to be in the middle here.
Along your deformation.
Along the deformation of your curve.
To fill this gap.
Then the next one is the optimization of the internal line.
The optimization of the internal line is actually easier to understand.
In the current new version, you can go to the settings.
For example, you have to go along.
When you create multiple internal lines through the internal line interface.
You can edit the distance between the two internal lines separately.
Or you can choose to directly connect both sides of a line.
Both sides of the line are deep into the internal line.
Then there is another option below.
Is to keep the curve.
What about keeping the curve?
It's like this.
In the same way as you use a line to create the internal line.
If you choose to keep the curve.
Then it will maintain.
The original direction of the line.
To add a lot of extra curve points.
In this case.
Although it can maintain this curve effect very well.
But it will add a lot.
It will add a lot of useless curve points.
If you choose not to keep the curve.
It can still generate a curve that is close to the previous curve.
Some internal lines.
But its internal points.
There won't be so many curve points.
The spiral version.
The spiral version is like this.
Let me say one more thing.
The spiral version.
Is used to make the river side.
Because of the spiral.
I want to see.
Because of the internal circle of the spiral.
That is.
You see this as the internal circle.
See this as the external circle.
Its difference is relatively large.
So you can pass.
You can imagine the spiral.
It is a pattern that is very good.
A pattern that is very good.
Then through this kind of good shape.
The pattern that is combined.
Through its internal and external insertions.
You can sew this whole edge.
To a.
For example, like a collar.
Or.
Well.
The position of the collar.
The position of the collar of the shirt.
Through the outer.
The length difference between the outer layer and the inner layer.
The length difference between the outer circle and the inner circle.
Let it form a fold.
It's a triangular fold.
You just imagine this pattern.
It's a lot of fan shapes.
Put them together.
Then it's the size of the virtual model.
In the new version.
In addition to being able to change the size of our default virtual model.
The pattern of the default virtual model.
That is.
Some patterns of the default virtual model.
Including the curve of its butt.
Or this butt.
It is.
The overall size is down or up.
This butt is flat.
It's more chubby.
Or.
Like.
The shape of the chest.
You can change it.
Okay.
Including the shoulder width of the chest.
And the height of the chest.
You can go.
According to the size of the default virtual model.
The last one.
It's the copy animation.
The copy animation.
In fact.
It's easier to understand.
That is.
When your copy.
Well.
Activated.
After the copy simulation.
The copy animation can also fall.
That is.
The copy animation.
It will make an independent animation layer.
It was recorded.
Well.
For example.
In the previous version.
Allow.
The copy.
With conflict.
Participate in the simulation.
In the new version.
You can.
Through this function.
To achieve.
When your copy.
First.
Your copy.
Is to activate.
In fact.
It can't.
Stick to the material with a glue tool.
It is.
A completely.
Heavy.
Conflict.
Model.
Participate.
In the 3D collision.
Then.
You can.
Record its current position.
Through the key.
So.
The current position.
In the middle.
It will have a linear change.
Then.
We.
Here.
Take a look.
If you.
This.
Anti-activate.
Then.
Because.
You are now.
To its state.
Changed.
It is no longer.
A state of participation simulation.
It will.
Wipe out.
Pre-participation simulation.
And.
Participate in collision.
One effect.
There is another.
If you.
Use the glue tool.
To stick it on.
Activate again.
First.
Record again.
This.
It.
Participate in the simulation.
Animation.
Because.
It.
To re-initiate.
Calculation.
There is one.
With the glue tool.
After.
You.
To it.
A copy of it.
The opening.
Record.
It.
Will not be.
In the middle.
For example.
I.
Now.
Move it.
To another.
Position.
Then.
Insert.
The key.
Some.
Including.
These.
Is.
Wearing.
Multiple.
Plates.
You.
Can.
Use.
This.
Function.
Let.
Him.
Participate.
In the simulation.
Thank you.
All the way.
For your support.
Thank you.
Tonight.
Participate.
In our.
Live.
Room.
Thank you.
All the way.
For the.
Support.
Thank you.
All the way.
For the.
Support.
If.
You.
Have.
What.
You.
Want.
To.
Watch.
Or.
Interested.
Want.
Us.
To.
Invite.
As.
Guests.
Friends.
Then.
You.
Can.
Give.
Us.
Comments.
Like.
Share.
Comments.
Thank you.
Good night.
Bye.